Guide to the Rice News photo files, 1995-2006 UA 357
Woodson Research Center, Rice University, Houston, Texas
- Series II: 2000-2006, 207065
  - Subseries A: 2000, 207066
    - February 3, 2000, 207070 (Box 12, Folder 5)
      Photographs and negatives include: the Winter Jazz Soiree, the Rice Jazz Ensemble, the Rice Social Dance Society, Richard Baraniuk, Jones Graduate School of Management, Spence Stephens, Scott Sitton, Morris Dees, Paul Katz, Malcolm Gillis, and Morris Dees.
    - February 10, 2000, 207071 (Box 12, Folder 6)
      Photographs and negatives include: Andre Watts, Andrea Metz, and Doug Daft.
    - February 17, 2000, 207072 (Box 12, Folder 7)
      Photographs and negatives include: Cars of the Future, Rice Environmental Conference, the Women's Resource Center fourth anniversary, Hardy Bourland, Service Awards, Frank Bearden, Malcolm Gillis, Russell Barnes, and the Reckling Park Grand Opening.
    - February 24, 2000, 207073 (Box 12, Folder 8)
      Photographs and negatives include: Gil Cuthbertson, Jose Aranda, Devika Subramanian, Elizabeth Long, Diversity Week, Tao Li, Reese Harvey, John Hempel, William Veech, John Polking, Thierry DePauw, Bob Hardt, Robin Forman, Tim Cochran, and the memorial service honoring Housotn firefighters Kimberly Ann Smith and Lewis Evans Mayo III.
    - March 2, 2000, 207074 (Box 12, Folder 9)
      Photographs and negatives include: Mae Jemison, Sidney Burrus, Jorma Lilleberg, Jim Allers, Owlchemy club, the Houston Museum of Natural Science, Roland Smith, and Iris Hurtado.
    - March 16, 2000, 207075 (Box 12, Folder 10)
      Photographs and negatives include: Delores McCall, Jerry McCall, the AIDS Memorial Quilt, Michael Hammond, Tom Hammond, FotoFest 2000 at the Rice University Art Gallery, and the "Clubs of Bamako" exhibit by Malick Sidibe.
    - March 23, 2000, 207076 (Box 12, Folder 11)
      Photographs and negatives include: Ken Jackson, Jenny Cafferty, Margaret Fox, Steve Lewis, James Harmon, and the Baker Institute think tank.
    - March 30, 2000, 207077 (Box 12, Folder 12)
      Photographs and negatives include: Willy Week and Robert Irwin.
    - April 6, 2000, 207078 (Box 12, Folder 13)
      Photographs and negatives include: Debbie Dickinson, Kathleen Kaun, Colleen Dutton, and Martel College.
    - April 13, 2000, 207079 (Box 12, Folder 14)
      Photographs and negatives include: Fay Yarbrough, Malcolm Gillis, Roland Smith, Tony Berning, Joon Choe, the Rice Chess Club, Herb Ward, and Jamila Nelson.
    - April 20, 2000, 207080 (Box 12, Folder 15)
      Photographs and negatives include: Malcolm Gillis, Willy's Pub, Jeff Barrie, Alex Tapia, Martel College groundbreaking, David Chen, Rebecca Bergquist, and Brian Huberman.
    - April 27, 2000, 207081 (Box 12, Folder 16)
      Photographs and negatives include: Urban Plunge, Steven Caufield, Arul Lingappan, Craig Harrison, Chris Sullivan, Maya Hazarika, Sarah Cloots, Laura Guerra-Cardus, Sumona Pramanik, Deanna Smith, Michael Erfe, John Hutchinson, Paula Hutchinson, Jenny Cafferty, Emma Hutchinson, Judy Le, the Study Abroad Photo Contest, and Katia Baizan's "Carnevale."
    - May 4, 2000, 207082 (Box 13, Folder 1)
      Photographs and negatives include: English as a Second Language courses for Rice staff, Yu-Li Sun, George Smith, Francisco Maldonado, Jessica Zuniga, Jose L. Leal, and Mia Pfleging.
    - May 11, 2000, 207083 (Box 13, Folder 2)
      Photographs and negatives include: Richard Stong, Julie Taylor, Richard Stoll, John Zammito, John Olson, Alan Grob, Chandler Davidson, Miquel Quinones, Zenaido Camacho, Mark Scheid, and the New Alumni Picnic.
    - May 25, 2000, 207084 (Box 13, Folder 3)
      Photographs and negatives include: Jonathan Borck, Milton Laufer, Andrew Hughes, Salil Patel, Shane Smith, Malcolm Gillis, George H. W. Bush, Rice University Art Gallery "Gigantor" exhibit by David Chien, Catherine Schowe, Norwegian tour, Krista Noack, Malcolm Gillis, Albert Kidd, Terry Koonce, and Bob Dalton.
    - June 29, 2000, 207085 (Box 13, Folder 4)
      Photographs and negatives include: Cynthia Joubert, Maria Elena Gracia, Barbara White, E. William Barnett, John Boles, James A. Baker III, Edward Djerejian, Bruce Riedel, Malcolm Gillis, and the groundbreaking of Jones Graduate School.
    - July 27, 2000, 207086 (Box 13, Folder 5)
      Photographs and negatives include: Gwen Aldridge, Darlene Banning, Nelson Correa, Rebecca Ledesma, Veronica Bernal, John Gomez, Mark Ditman, Russell Price, Allen Harrison, Beverley Konzem, Jones School construction, Alexis Latner, Ben Fonbuena Jr., Phillip Salinas, Ellen Butler, Shiliang Chang, Celi Zuniga, B.J. Almond, and Jennifer Evans.
    - August 31, 2000, 207087 (Box 13, Folder 6)
      Photographs and negatives include: the National Society of Hispanic MBAs, Martha Salinas, Houston Hispanic Professionals' Leadership Day, Rice matriculation, Allen Matusow, Rice University Police Officers, National Night Out, Pete Martinez, Dennis Senter, Natalie McDuell, and Rice athletic camps.
    - September 7, 2000, 207088 (Box 13, Folder 7)
      Photographs and negatives include: Flor Gutierrez, English as a Second Language classes, Heather Masden, Marie Magee, and Maxine Turner.
    - September 14, 2000, 207089 (Box 13, Folder 8)
      Photographs and negatives include: Graduate Student Association fall picnic, Valhalla, Phillip Salinas, Marcia Citron, Russell Price, Mark Ditman, Paul Rodarte, Lydia Gonzales, Malcolm Gillis, and Jeff Bezos.
    - September 21, 2000, 207090 (Box 13, Folder 9)
      Photographs and negatives include: Neal Lane, Barber Day, James Arellano, and Ben Gerdemann.
    - September 28, 2000, 207091 (Box 13, Folder 10)
      Photographs and negatives include: Rice School of Architecture reconstruction.
    - October 5, 2000, 207092 (Box 13, Folder 11)
      Photographs and negatives include: Outdoor art, Mark Ramont, Trish Rigdon, and Lindsay Batsford.
    - October 12, 2000, 207093 (Box 13, Folder 12)
      Photographs and negatives include: Rice University Art Gallery, the Museum District Day, remote clickers in class, and Alan Chapman.
    - October 19, 2000, 207094 (Box 13, Folder 13)
      Photographs and negatives include: the Martel College Founding Committee, Gavin Parks, Victoria Zyp, Matthew Bentley, Rene Aninao, Emily Venson, Joseph Ndu, Meghan Miller, Andrew Swinich, Luis Rodriguez, David Cerutti, Arthur Few, Joan Few, Karen George, Cynthia Lu, Evie Zambetakis, Ricky Kalra, Mindy Tyson, Jessica Contreras, Jonathan Behr, Brad Glock, Rice Technology Education Center, Continuing Studies, and the Rice Center for Career Development chili cook-off.
    - October 26, 2000, 207095 (Box 13, Folder 14)
      Photographs and negatives include: Michael Emerson.
    - November 2, 2000, 207096 (Box 13, Folder 15)
      Photographs and negatives include: Malcolm Gillis, Julian Navarrete, Gertrude Ealey, Elaine Sciolino, Deloitte and Touche donation, Richard L. Avant, Jeff Bornstein, Katie Pavlovsky, Morris Dees, and Michael Ford.
    - November 9, 2000, 207097 (Box 14, Folder 1)
      Photographs and negatives include: Rice Homecoming, Lewis Lockwood, Dava Sobel, and the President's Lecture.
    - November 16, 2000, 207098 (Box 14, Folder 2)
      Photographs and negatives include: Doug Tomlinson, Harvest Handoff and Baking Contest with the Houston Food Bank, Bill Hodges, Eve Bower, Ebonee Butler, Ta-Shina Williams, Ryann Ferguson, Grace Hu, Brooke Lathram, Tyson Pillow, dedication of the Berlin Wall Monument, Edward Djerejian, Juergen Chrobog, Malcolm Gillis, Hanno von Graevenitz, Nicholas Triedo, "Ebano 2000" exhibit at the Rice Media Center, the Hope and Harmony Unity Forum, Ballet Folklorico, and the Office of Multicultural Affairs.
    - November 30, 2000, 207099 (Box 14, Folder 3)
      Photographs and negatives include: Russell Pitman, Alma Guillermoprieto, John Alford, Earl Black, William Martin, Paul Brace, Robert Stein, William Hobby, Tyson Pillow, Joe Cavallaro, Gene Frantz, Patrick Frantz, Hyeokho Choi, The Evolution of Mexican-American Music, and Tony Diaz.
    - December 7, 2000, 207100 (Box 14, Folder 4)
      Photographs and negatives include: Kade Smith, Zanna Fredland, "Amahl and the Night Visitors," Antonios Mikos, Eva Haverkamp, Jeff Hoye, and Derek Ruths.
  - Subseries B: 2001, 207101
    - January 11, 2001, 207102 (Box 14, Folder 5)
      Photographs and negatives include: Malcolm Gillis, Shirley Redwine, Lee Brown, Bill Archer, Rice Society of Automotive Engineers, and Natalye Appel.
    - January 18, 2001, 207103 (Box 14, Folder 6)
      Photographs and negatives include: and the "Time and the Presidency" exhibit at the Baker Institute.
    - January 25, 2001, 207104 (Box 14, Folder 7)
      Photographs and negatives include: Jeff Dee, OwlCon, the Alliance club at Rice, Carlos Garcia, and the Martin Luther King Jr. candlelight vigil.
    - February 1, 2001, 207105 (Box 14, Folder 8)
      Photographs and negatives include: William A. Lawson, Malcolm Gillis, James A. Baker III, President's Lecture series, and Hugh Sidney.
    - February 8, 2001, 207106 (Box 14, Folder 9)
      Photographs and negatives include: Mary Ann Reed, Jose Zarazua, Maximo Umanzor, Chris Huston, Rice Women's Soccer Team, Justin Singer, Mercedes Paul, Ketan Gangatirkar, Mikell Motive, Jim Baylor, the Rice Whistle Campaign, the Women's Resource Center, Students Organized Against Rape, Malcom Gillis, and Kim Dae Jung.
    - February 15, 2001, 207107 (Box 14, Folder 10)
      Photographs and negatives include: Faculty and staff retirees, Suzanne King, Anand Kumar, and Priyank Jaiswal.
    - February 22, 2001, 207108 (Box 14, Folder 11)
      Photographs and negatives include: NAMES Project AIDS Memorial Quilt, Kenny Baugh, Rice Owls Baseball Team, Mona Hicks, the Women's Resource Center fifth anniversary, Amanda Gor, Megan McGehee, Hilary Young, Desrey Clementine Fox, Michelle Precourt, Sarah Pitre, Lindsay Botsford, Delia Wendel, Kimberly Dawn Riggins, Nia Georges, Rebecca Bergquist, Ilse Guzman, Elle Marie Schollenberger, Michelle Brand, Felicia Cavallini, Lindsay Smith, Tricia Mitchell Kim, Lindsay Germano, Catherine Yi-Yu Cho Woo, and the "Unity in Diversity" week Culture Fair.
    - March 1, 2001, 207109 (Box 14, Folder 12)
      Photographs and negatives include: Jake Charkey, Renee Block, Unity in Diversity Week, Stephen Zeff, Malcolm Gillis, John Myung, Yong-Gun Jon, Hyong-Chul Li, Okjuo Myung, Suchan Chae, and Patricia Churchland.
    - March 15, 2001, 207110 (Box 14, Folder 13)
      Photographs and negatives include: the Rice Undergraduate Scholars Program, Jim Kinsey, Don Johnson, and Jim Pomerantz.
    - March 22, 2001, 207111 (Box 14, Folder 14)
      Photographs and negatives include: Dennis Lee, "Angles and Attitudes: An Exploration of Women" exhibit at Farnsworth Pavilion, Plant Swap, Carolynne White, Pat Kambhu, and the Center for Education Classroom Storytelling Program.
    - March 29, 2001, 207112 (Box 14, Folder 15)
      Photographs and negatives include: Nancy Carrasco, Alex Ruiz, Children's Museum of Houston, and the Rice Association of Biologically Inclined Students.
    - April 5, 2001, 207113 (Box 14, Folder 16)
      Photographs and negatives include: Frank Lloyd Wright exhibit at the Rice School of Architecture, Greg Hillis, Anne Klein, and "A Midsummer Night's Dream" by the Shepherd School Opera and the Shepherd School Chamber Orchestra.
    - April 12, 2001, 207114 (Box 14, Folder 17)
      Photographs and negatives include: Carolyn Hoxby, Beer Bike, Jones College, the Rice Philharmonics, and the Amherst Zumbyes.
    - April 19, 2001, 207115 (Box 15, Folder 1)
      Photographs and negatives include: Jared Diamond, and the President's Lecture Series.
    - April 26, 2001, 207116 (Box 15, Folder 2)
      Photographs and negatives include: Audrey Ette, the Black Student Association, Racial Solidarity Week, Chandler Davidson, Malcolm Gillis, David French, Gordon Bethune, Ick Jin, the Gulf War exhibit at Baker Institute.
    - May 3, 2001, 207117 (Box 15, Folder 3)
      Photographs and negatives include: Guarav Oberoi, the Senior Committee, Katherine Swanson, President of Ireland Mary McAleese, and the Baker Institute.
    - May 10, 2001, 207118 (Box 15, Folder 4)
      Photographs and negatives include: John Zammito, Alex Ferrance, Miguel Rodriguez, Anthony Brandt, Richard Spuler, Walter Chapman, Steve Cox, Richard Baraniuk, John Olson, Mickey Quinones, Ian Gruber, and John Ambler.
    - May 24, 2001, 207119 (Box 15, Folder 5)
      Photographs and negatives include: Michael Sew Hoy, Robert Jump, Robert Glazewski, Patrick Frantz, Kurt Sanner, Joseph Blocher, Jose Narbona, and commencement.
    - June 28, 2001, 207120 (Box 15, Folder 6)
      Photographs and negatives include: Susan Lieberman, Christine Adams, Mark Gardner, Doug Tomlinson, Mary Ruth Kubricht, Richard Stearman, Eugen Radulescu, Eric Valentine, Don Hudlow, Rice University Police Department cleaning up after Tropical Storm Allison, National Bike to Work Day, Greg Marshall, Mark Goldberg, Bill Taylor, Gordon Quan, Ken Nipe, and Robert Stein.
    - July 26, 2001, 207121 (Box 15, Folder 7)
      Photographs and negatives include: wooden bench replacement, Fort Bend Independent School District, Mariette Bellamy, Dee Koch, Bernie Mathes, Connie Floyd, Mary Jackson, Rosa Garay, Sherry Ziegner, and Jana Callan.
    - August 30, 2001, 207122 (Box 15, Folder 8)
      Photographs and negatives include: O-Week, Adam Stepinski, Rice matriculation, Malcolm Gillis, Zenaido Camacho, and the Ice Cream Social.
    - September 6, 2001, 207123 (Box 15, Folder 9)
      Photographs and negatives include: Universidad Zamorano, Kiley Athanasiou, Malcolm Gillis, Albert Kidd, Terry Koonce, Minerva Gonzales, Sandra Veliz, Miraya Gonzales, National Night Out, and the Rice University Police Department.
    - September 13, 2001, 207124 (Box 15, Folder 10)
      Photographs and negatives include: Nelson Correa, Hanszen College, Wiess College, the Rice Career Services Center Employer Advisory Board (Center for Career Development), Melissa Waldon, Sharyl Hackett, Cheryl Matherly, Tim Meyer, Bill Burton, Nancy Laidlaw, Jackie Hing, Mark Courtney, Jeff Johannigman, Heidi Glantzberg, Bruce Baehl, Mark Finger, Ken May, and Jeff Andrien.
    - September 20, 2001, 207125 (Box 15, Folder 11)
      Photographs and negatives include: Bill Martin, Gavin Parks, Jamie Lisagor, Miles Scotcher, Malcolm Gillis, and 9/11 observance.
    - September 27, 2001, 207126 (Box 15, Folder 12)
      Photographs and negatives include: Graduate Student Association blood drive for victims of 9/11, and Alvin R. Tarlov.
    - October 4, 2001, 207127 (Box 15, Folder 13)
      Photographs and negatives include: outdoor art classes, Lovett Hall, School of Architecture, and furniture designed by Lars Lerup.
    - October 11, 2001, 207128 (Box 15, Folder 14)
      Photographs and negatives include: forum by ADVANCE (Advocating Diversity and the Need for Cultural Exploration) and the Muslim Students Association, patriotism after 9/11, Kathy Felker, David Cook, Mahmoud El-Gamal, Ussama Makdisi, Allen Matusow, and Paula Sanders.
    - October 18, 2001, 207129 (Box 15, Folder 15)
      Photographs and negatives include: massages at the health fair for students, and Rebecca Wenham.
    - October 25, 2001, 207130 (Box 15, Folder 16)
      Photographs and negatives include: Susan Wood, the Modernist Studies Association, and Marshall Needleman Armintor.
    - November 1, 2001, 207131 (Box 15, Folder 17)
      Photographs and negatives include: the second annual Harvest Handoff Food Drive and Baking Contest for the Houston Food Bank, Richard Tapia, and the Recruitment Into College Education Through Minority Scholarships Fund (RICE-TMS) merit scholars.
    - November 8, 2001, 207132 (Box 15, Folder 18)
      Photographs and negatives include: Willy's statue wearing a jack-o-lantern for Halloween.
    - November 15, 2001, 207133 (Box 15, Folder 19)
      Photographs and negatives include: Andy Barron, the Norman Hackerman Award in Chemical Research, Pierre Jalbert, Alex Knapp, Sara Stevens, School of Architecture, and Pate's Drive In.
    - November 29, 2001, 207134 (Box 15, Folder 20)
      Photographs and negatives include: students on 180, the Hispanic Association for Cultural Enrichment at Rice (HACER) Day of the Dead ofrenda for victims of 9/11, Baruch Brody, Shirley Bland, Christine Mueller, Rice Recycles Day, Richard L. Avant of Deloitte and Touche, Malcolm Gillis, and Libby Larsen.
    - December 6, 2001, 207135 (Box 16, Folder 1)
      Photographs and negatives include: Mark Ditman, Graduate Student Apartments, Marilyn Hellums, FoFo Lewis, the Holiday Bazaar, Zenaido Camacho, Audrey Ette, Malcom Gillis, and Nambaryn Enkhbayar.
  - Subseries C: 2002, 207136
    - January 10, 2002, 207137 (Box 16, Folder 2)
      Photographs and negatives include: Julia Benz, Mercedes Flores, Wah Chiu, John Kolb, Malcolm Gillis, John Stobo, John Mendelsohn, Ralph Feigin, Arthur Smith, James Willerson, and Kathleen Matthews.
    - January 17, 2002, 207138 (Box 16, Folder 3)
      Photographs and negatives include: Chad Bhatti, Blair Christian, Rudy Fink, Joan Moore, Henny Halliburton, Rayzor Hall, Nursultan Nazarbayev, and Edward Djerejian.
    - January 24, 2002, 207139 (Box 16, Folder 4)
      Photographs and negatives include: Gary Smith, Michael Hammond, and Colleen Dutton.
    - January 31, 2002, 207140 (Box 16, Folder 5)
      Photographs and negatives include: the Martin Luther King Jr. candlelight vigil, Lee Brown, the Black Student Association, Aliaquanda Derrick, the Melodious Voices of Praise, Rev. Renwick Gilmore, Audrey Ette, Adam Brickman, John Glassmire, and Radio Free Sid.
    - February 7, 2002, 207141 (Box 16, Folder 6)
      Photographs and negatives include: Martel College opening, J.D. Bucky Allshouse, D. Kent Anderson, Eric Johnson, Laura Gardner, Science Olympiad, and Cortnie Voncourt.
    - February 14, 2002, 207142 (Box 16, Folder 7)
      Photographs and negatives include: Ron Pinkerton, and OwlCon.
    - February 21, 2002, 207143 (Box 16, Folder 8)
      Photographs and negatives include: Eliza Lovett Randall, John Boles, Melinda Sue Hutchings, Sara Lowman, Karen Hess Rogers, Edward Djerejian, Vaira Vike-Freiberga, the Women's Resource Center Impact Awards, Jessica Foster, Laura Gardner, Izamara Gamez, Les Hulsey, Shayda Naficy, Audrey Ette, Phillippa Angelides, Rebecca Baldwin, Megan Arendt, Kristine Wallace, Jamie Lisagor, Umbelina Cantu, Kate Floyd, Vianna Davila, Jones College magister house, Alan Grob, Elizabeth Baber, James Castaneda, and Walter Isle.
    - February 28, 2002, 207144 (Box 16, Folder 9)
      Photographs and negatives include: John Elliot, Department of Kinesiology, Jose Enrique Cruz, Hunter Brown, Enrique Barrera, and the Say YES To a Youngster's Future program with the Houston Independent School District.
    - March 14, 2002, 207145 (Box 16, Folder 10)
      Photographs and negatives include: Lunar New Year, the Rice Chinese Student Association, and the Rice Baseball team.
    - March 21, 2002, 207146 (Box 16, Folder 11)
      Photographs and negatives include: Autry Court construction, Julia Amborski, Thomas Hammond, Malcolm Gillis, and Shepherd School tributes to Michael Hammond.
    - March 28, 2002, 207147 (Box 16, Folder 12)
      Photographs and negatives include: the annual Culture Fair, Dan DeHanas, Akiko Hosokawa, Beer Bike, Bucky Allshouse, Cokie Roberts, and Steve Roberts.
    - April 4, 2002, 207148 (Box 16, Folder 13)
      Photographs and negatives include: Ryan Harlan, Ruthann Gairdner, Disability Support Services, Rebecca Perry, Malcolm Gillis, the Houston Technology Forum, Neal Lane, Richard Smalley, Jim Tour, and Jennifer West.
    - April 11, 2002, 207149 (Box 17, Folder 1)
      Photographs and negatives include: Malcolm Gillis, Kay Bailey Hutchison, and Ray Miller.
    - April 18, 2002, 207150 (Box 17, Folder 2)
      CD and photographs include: Bond Kick Off pictures, and the dedication of Martel College.
    - April 25, 2002, 207151 (Box 17, Folder 3)
      Photographs, CD, and negatives include: James Burke, Malcolm Gillis, Kaye Stripling, David Minter, Good Morning America, Christel Miller, and Jaime Rios.
    - May 2, 2002, 207152 (Box 17, Folder 4)
      Photographs and negatives include: Phil Bedient.
    - May 9, 2002, 207153 (Box 17, Folder 5)
      Photographs and negatives include: John Ambler, William Camfield, John Dennis, Steven Cox, Michael Gustin, Chandler Davidson, John Zammito, Terrence Doody, Mikki Hebl, Keith Krumwiede, 15th Annual Art Car Parade, and the Marching Owl Band.
    - May 23, 2002, 207154 (Box 17, Folder 6)
      Photographs and negatives include: Kristin Krukenberg, Allison Dennis, Jennie Kaya, Elizabeth Baber, and Sarah Lowman.
    - June 27, 2002, 207155 (Box 17, Folder 7)
      Photographs and negatives include: annual Bike-to-Work Day.
    - July 25, 2002, 207156 (Box 17, Folder 8)
      Photographs and negatives not currently available.
    - August 29, 2002, 207157 (Box 17, Folder 9)
      Photographs include: Ken Hatfield, Dana Dimel, the Gulf Coast Regional Blood Center's 2002 Administaff Bayou Bucket Blood Drive, Rice University new Web site, Rice matriculation, O-Week, and John Hutchinson.
    - September 5, 2002, 207158 (Box 17, Folder 10)
      Photographs and negatives include: Les Hulsey, Phil Hassell, and Farrel Locklin.
    - September 12, 2002, 207159 (Box 17, Folder 11)
      Photographs and negatives include: George Hirasaki, Jiansheng Chen, and Ken Nipe.
    - September 19, 2002, 207160 (Box 17, Folder 12)
      Photographs and contents include: September 11 memorial, Rice Chorale, Skye Donovan, Thomas Jaber, Germany's "Golden Twenties" exhibit through Rice's Goethe Center.
    - September 26, 2002, 207161 (Box 17, Folder 13)
      Photographs and negatives include: Jones Graduate School of Management dedication, L.E. Simmons, D. Kent Anderson, Malcolm Gillis, Gilbert Whitaker, Bernard Fields, and E. William Barnett.
    - October 3, 2002, 207162 (Box 17, Folder 14)
      Photographs and negatives include: Teveia Barnes, Mary Lou Margrave, the Faculty Women's Club, the Graduate Loan Closet, Malcolm Gillis, Helen Toombs, and the Conference for Rice Alumni Leaders.
    - October 10, 2002, 207163 (Box 17, Folder 15)
      Photographs and negatives include: James Prohaska, John Boles, the Century Scholars program, Alan Pham, and the "Smackdown the Vote" event.
    - October 17, 2002, 207164 (Box 17, Folder 16)
      Photographs and negatives include: Melissa Raz, Jill Ponasik, Denise Stom, Dalma Boronkai, Brenda Arredondo, Aracely Morales, Rice's English as a Second Language Tutoring Program, and the new Wiess college.
    - October 24, 2002, 207165 (Box 18, Folder 1)
      Photographs and negatives include: the Shepherd School of Music, Enso Quartet, Tereza Stanislav, Maureen Nelson, Robert Brophy, Richard Belcher, and Harold Shapiro.
    - October 31, 2002, 207166 (Box 18, Folder 2)
      Photographs and negatives include: the Harvest Handoff and Baking Contest.
    - November 7, 2002, 207167 (Box 18, Folder 3)
      Photographs and negatives include: Grant Sazuki, and the "Bamboo Roof" installation at the Rice University Art Gallery by Shigeru Ban.
    - November 14, 2002, 207168 (Box 18, Folder 4)
      Photographs include: Lisa Fikes, Andrew Cates, Rice student athletes, the Elizabeth Gillis Award for Exemplary Service, Suzanne King, Elizabeth Gillis, Sue Hutchings, Yao Ming, Malcolm Gillis, Deloitte and Touche, Amy Sutton, Jill Thompson, Richard Avant, and Susan Sample.
    - November 21, 2002, 207169 (Box 18, Folder 5)
      Photographs and negatives include: Jen Cooper, Rice Women's Soccer, and Malcolm Gillis.
    - December 5, 2002, 207170 (Box 18, Folder 6)